[{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664137556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":10713,"timeElapsed":39803},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664143083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":5526,"timeElapsed":45330},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664149918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6835,"timeElapsed":52165},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664153241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3321,"timeElapsed":55487},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664156896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3654,"timeElapsed":59143},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664161668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4771,"timeElapsed":63915},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664164180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2511,"timeElapsed":66427},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664165857,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1676,"timeElapsed":68104},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664167402,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1545,"timeElapsed":69649},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664172096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3996,"timeElapsed":74343},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664173452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1355,"timeElapsed":75699},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664176013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2559,"timeElapsed":78259},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664178482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2469,"timeElapsed":80729},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664180523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2040,"timeElapsed":82770},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664182185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1660,"timeElapsed":84432},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664186126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3940,"timeElapsed":88373},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664187593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1467,"timeElapsed":89840},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664189815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2221,"timeElapsed":92062},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664193654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3068,"timeElapsed":95901},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664196389,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2734,"timeElapsed":98636},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664204196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7806,"timeElapsed":106443},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664206287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2090,"timeElapsed":108534},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664214447,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":8160,"timeElapsed":116694},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664215971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1523,"timeElapsed":118218},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664217783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1811,"timeElapsed":120030},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664219665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1881,"timeElapsed":121912},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664221385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1719,"timeElapsed":123632},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664223057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":1671,"timeElapsed":125304},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664226753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2930,"timeElapsed":129000},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664228526,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1772,"timeElapsed":130773},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664230376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1849,"timeElapsed":132623},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664232271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1894,"timeElapsed":134518},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664234307,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2035,"timeElapsed":136554},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664236049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1741,"timeElapsed":138296},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664240538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4488,"timeElapsed":142785},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664242193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":1653,"timeElapsed":144440},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664243943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":1750,"timeElapsed":146190},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664264431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":19732,"timeElapsed":166678},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664266233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1801,"timeElapsed":168480},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664268686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2452,"timeElapsed":170933},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664271412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2725,"timeElapsed":173659},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664273051,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1638,"timeElapsed":175298},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664274375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1323,"timeElapsed":176622},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664276963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2587,"timeElapsed":179210},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664278470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":1506,"timeElapsed":180717},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664279969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1498,"timeElapsed":182216},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664285221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4048,"timeElapsed":187468},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664287353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2131,"timeElapsed":189600},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664288436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1082,"timeElapsed":190683},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664289570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1133,"timeElapsed":191817},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664291347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1776,"timeElapsed":193594},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664292890,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1542,"timeElapsed":195137},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664295195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2304,"timeElapsed":197442},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664297139,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":1943,"timeElapsed":199386},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664299337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2197,"timeElapsed":201584},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664306105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5817,"timeElapsed":208352},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664307544,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1438,"timeElapsed":209791},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664310036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2491,"timeElapsed":212283},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664311353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1317,"timeElapsed":213600},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664313456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2102,"timeElapsed":215703},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664315327,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1870,"timeElapsed":217574},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664318053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2725,"timeElapsed":220300},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664319356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1302,"timeElapsed":221603},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664321427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2070,"timeElapsed":223674},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664325776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3276,"timeElapsed":228023},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664326979,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":1202,"timeElapsed":229226},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664328170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1190,"timeElapsed":230417},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664329631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1460,"timeElapsed":231878},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664331271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1640,"timeElapsed":233518},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664333884,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2612,"timeElapsed":236131},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664338601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4716,"timeElapsed":240848},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664340306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1704,"timeElapsed":242553},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664341834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1527,"timeElapsed":244081},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664343386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1551,"timeElapsed":245633},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664350592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":6361,"timeElapsed":252839},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664351722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":1129,"timeElapsed":253969},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664353578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1855,"timeElapsed":255825},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664357450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3871,"timeElapsed":259697},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664359629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2178,"timeElapsed":261876},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664360990,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1360,"timeElapsed":263237},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664364491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3500,"timeElapsed":266738},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664366129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1637,"timeElapsed":268376},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664368217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2087,"timeElapsed":270464},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664373177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4162,"timeElapsed":275424},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664374008,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":830,"timeElapsed":276255},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664375182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":1173,"timeElapsed":277429},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664376138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":955,"timeElapsed":278385},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664377126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":987,"timeElapsed":279373},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664378066,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":939,"timeElapsed":280313},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664380484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2417,"timeElapsed":282731},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664381611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":1127,"timeElapsed":283858},{"subjectID":"78vfso1xfo","prolificID":"6750c7eaec05ae2f773b5be9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742163ea9a49a640662c8b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664383279,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1668,"timeElapsed":285526}]